Sickness has a new name.
The Hospital is a horror film directed by None.
Leopold's Hospital has many urban legends surrounding it, but the residents of
Bridgeport all agree on one thing: tortured souls roam its abandoned halls.
The mystery proves too much for a pretty young student who
decides to investigate for her senior class project.
Unfortunately, she does not find ghosts.
She, instead, finds Stanley...
serial rapist, murderer, and psychopath.
As the young girl becomes Stanley's new pet, a team of young investigators descend on the
hospital to "hunt some ghosts." Stanley sees nothing but fun and games in his future.
But, what Stanley does not know is that the hospital truly is haunted and the
restless spirits there are not happy with what he has been doing.
The Hospital is a 2013 horror film co-directed by
Tommy Golden and Daniel Emery Taylor.
Having a limited US release in February 2013, the film has subsequently screened at various horror film festivals, was presented at
Cannes Film Festival, and took home the "Scariest Movie" award at Germany's largest genre festival, Movie Days, in Dortmund.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.